reinvigorate.net 2010-06-11

# Privacy : Reinvigorate

## Privacy Policy

We collect personal information in a number of ways when you visit our site or use our service. For example, you provide us with personal information when you register for an account or contact us by email. Reinvigorate automatically receives and records information from your browser, including your IP address and cookies. The personal information collected is used for billing, identification, authentication, service improvement, research, and contact.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from our servers and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to access information when you sign in, store your preferences, and to keep you logged in. You can configure your browser to accept or reject these cookies.

### Information Sharing

We do not sell, rent or share personal information with third parties without your prior consent. We may, however, disclose personal information when we believe it violates our Terms of Service or is appropriate to comply with the law, to protect our or our users' rights, as well as to protect our users from fraudulent, abusive, and unlawful use of our site. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

### Information Security

We restrict access to personal information to Reinvigorate employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our service. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

### Changes

Reinvigorate will notify customers by email about any significant changes in this policy.

### Privacy Questions / Feedback

If you have questions or concerns about Reinvigorate's Privacy Policy please contact us at [support@reinvigorate.net](mailto:support@reinvigorate.net)
